(Sheldon:)That proves nothing.
- Ready to go to lunch?
- Do you think I'm feminine?
- Yeah, let's go.
- Thanks a lot.
- What's going on?
- I broke down and I read Lucy's blog.
(Raj:)In one of the entries she said when we
first met, I struck her as a little feminine.
(Howard:)Just a little? That's great.
(Raj:)I have to talk to her about this.
Ahh. Jeez, why do you girls always want
to talk about things?
(Howard:)Listen to me, if she's writing about
your relationship, use it to your advantage.
(Howard:)- Rig the game.
- That doesn't seem fair.
(Howard:)Is it fair that girls like confident,
normal guys more than nervous weirdos?
(Raj:)No, it's not.
I've always thought that was unfair.
(Howard:)So take what's in that blog
and use it to get her pants off.
Why do you make everything filthy?
Why couldn't you say the blog is like...
(Raj:)...her giving me the key to her heart?
"The key to her heart." Heh. That's nice.